

Profile

A loving, flexible and hardworking Registered Nurse with 3 years experience in planning, coordinating and managing the clinical services in paediatric nursing units. Responsible for the coordination and of nursing care and services provided to patients in the various units while facilitating the interdisciplinary team. Experienced in care and treatment involved individuals with a variety of physical, emotional, mental and psychiatric disabilities.

Employment History

Nurse Educator and Coordinator at GMCH 32, Chandigarh February 2017 — May 2018

Staff Nurse at Ananthapuri Hospitals and Research Institute , Trivandrum

May 2013 — March 2015

Education

BSc Nursing, CSI College of Nursing, Karakkonam

October 2008 — December 2012

+2, New Higher Secondary School, Trivandrum

June 2006 — March 2008

SSLC, Govt HS, Pappanamcode, Trivandrum

March 2006

Proffessional Registration

Kerala Nurses and Midwives Council, RN/RM 59255

March 2013 — March 2019

Courses

Awareness in Computer Concepts, NIELIT

October 2018

Basic Life Support

Code Blue Training

Job Responsiblities

- · Provide nursing care services under supervision
- · Provide direct patient care
- · Monitor the health of the patient
- · Maintain and update health records via the electronic system
- Conveying plans of care

Details

#515/1, Phase 6, SAS Nagar, Mohali, 160055, 9656520547 anjuc709@gmail.com

Date of birth 25/05/1991

Skills

Patient Care

Acute Care

Treatment Planning

Clinical Experience

Critical Care

Nurse Management

Ventillator Care

Languages

English

Hindi

Malayalam

- Provide care under the prescribed treatment plan
- Assess the patient consistent with the Public Health Practice Reference,
 Nursing Scope and Standards of Practice
- Observe and report on the well-being of patients
- Keep a record of each patient about their medical histories and their symptoms
- Operate medical equipment
- Administer medicines to patients
- Administer treatments to patients
- Teach your patients about managing their injury or illness
- Develop nursing care treatment plans
- Treat patients for their injury or illness
- · Educate patients about their health
- Provide leadership by delegating, supervising and participating in safe nursing care activities
- Supervise other staff, including other nurses
- · Administer medications and injections
- Assist doctors
- Assess the condition of patients
- Develop treatment plans for patients
- Discuss treatment plans and explain their conditions to the patient
- Oversee patient records
- Evaluate the patient care and identify opportunities for improvement
- Collaborate with the healthcare team
- Utilize all available resources to provide quality cost-effective patient care
- Serve as a role model/preceptor to new graduate nurses and less experienced personnel
- Data collection and analysis.
- Maintained all necessary documentation and clinical records of all the case patients per day, following office procedures while focusing on patient confidentiality.

1 References

Mrs. D. Usha Bai from Ananthapuri Hospitals and Research Institute ananthapurihri@vsnl.net · 04712506565

Dr Deepak Chawla from GMCH 32

Dept of Pediatrics · 01722621559